So, let us go back to our neural network with our weights and our input.
我们再次回到含有权重和输入的神经网络
And recall that the weights with superscript 1 belong to the first layer,
回想一下 含有上标 1 的权重属于第一层
and the weights with superscript 2 belong to the second layer.
含有上标 2 的权重属于第二层
Also, recall that the bias is not called b anymore.
偏差不再叫做 b
Now, it is called W31,
现在为了方便称为 w31
W32 etc. for convenience,
w32 等等
so that we can have everything in matrix notation.
所以我们把一切都用矩阵符号表示
And now what happens with the input?
现在怎么处理输入呢？
So, let us do the feedforward process.
我们来进行前馈过程
In the first layer,
在第一层中
we take the input and multiply it by the weights and that gives us h1,
我们利用输入 把它乘以权重 得到 h1
which is a linear function of the input and the weights.
这是输入和权重的线性函数
Same thing with h2,
同样 h2
given by this formula over here.
通过这个公式可以得到
Now, in the second layer,
现在 在第二层中
we would take this h1 and h2 and the new bias,
我们利用 h1 和 h2 以及新的偏差
apply the sigmoid function,
应用 sigmoid 函数
and then apply a linear function to them by multiplying them by
然后对它们应用线性函数 用它们乘以
the weights and adding them to get a value of h. And finally,
权重 添加值 h
in the third layer,
最后在第三层中
we just take a sigmoid function of h to get
我们只是利用 h 的 sigmoid 函数
our prediction or probability between 0 and 1, which is ŷ.
得到 0 到 1 之间的预测或概率 也就是 y-hat
And we can read this in more condensed notation by saying that
我们以更加浓缩的符号法这样写
the matrix corresponding to the first layer is W superscript 1,
认为第一层对应的矩阵是 W1 (1 为上标)
the matrix corresponding to the second layer is W superscript 2,
第二层对应的矩阵是 W2 (2 为上标)
and then the prediction we had is just going to be
那么我们得到的预测等于
the sigmoid of W superscript 2 combined with
σ W2 (2 为上标)
the sigmoid of W superscript 1 applied to the input x and that is feedforward.
和 σ W1 (1 为上标) (x) 这是前馈
Now, we are going to develop backpropagation,
现在我们要进行反向传播
which is precisely the reverse of feedforward.
也就是前馈的反向过程
So, we are going to calculate the derivative of
那么我们要使用链式法则
this error function with respect to each of the weights in
计算标签中每个权重
the labels by using the chain rule.
误差函数的导数
So, let us recall that our error function is this formula over here,
我们想到误差函数是这里的公式
which is a function of the prediction ŷ.
也就是预测 y-hat
But, since the prediction is a function of all the weights wij,
不过 因为预测是所有权重 wij 的函数
then the error function can be seen as the function on all the wij.
那么误差函数可以看做所有 wij 的函数
Therefore, the gradient is simply the vector formed by
所以梯度是向量
all the partial derivatives of the error function E with respect to each of the weights.
通过每个权重对应的误差函数 E 的偏导数得到结果
So, let us calculate one of these derivatives.
我们来计算其中一个导数
Let us calculate derivative of E with respect to W11 superscript 1.
计算 W11 (上标 1) E 的导数
So, since the prediction is simply a composition of functions and by the chain rule,
因为预测是函数的组合 通过链式法则
we know that the derivative with respect to this
我们知道了它的导数
is the product of all the partial derivatives.
是所有偏导数的乘积
In this case, the derivative E with respect
在这个例子中 W11 的导数 E
to W11 is the derivative of either respect to ŷ times
是 y-hat 对应的导数乘以
the derivative ŷ with respect to h
h 对应的导数 y-hat
times the derivative h with respect to h1 times the derivative h1 with respect to W11.
乘以 h1 对应的导数 h 乘以 W11 对应的导数 h1
This may seem complicated,
这可能看起来很复杂
but the fact that we can calculate a derivative of
不过我们可以通过四个偏导数的乘法
such a complicated composition function by just
计算这个复杂的复合函数导数
multiplying 4 partial derivatives is remarkable.
这是值得注意的
Now, we have already calculated the first one,
现在我们已经计算了第一个导数
the derivative of E with respect to ŷ.
y-hat 对应 E 的导数
And if you remember, we got ŷ minus y.
如果你还记得 我们求出了 y-hat 减去 y
So, let us calculate the other ones.
我们来计算其他几个
Let us zoom in a bit and look at just one piece of our multi-layer perceptron.
我们放大一下 观察多层感知器其中的一部分
The inputs are some values h1 and h2,
输入是一些值 h1 和 h2
which are values coming in from before.
这是之前得到的值
And once we apply the sigmoid and a linear function
一旦对 h1 和 h2 以及偏置单元对应的 1
on h1 and h2 and 1 corresponding to the biased unit,
应用 sigmoid 和线性函数
we get a result h. So,
我们会得到结果 h
now what is the derivative of h with respect to h1?
那么 h1 对应的导数 h 是什么呢？
Well, h is a sum of three things and only one of them contains h1.
h 是三项的总和 其中只有一个包含 h1
So, the second and the third summon just give us a derivative of 0.
那么第二个和第三个求和可以得到 0 的导数
The first summon gives us W11 superscript 2 because that is a constant,
第一个求和可以得到 W11 (上标 2) 因为这是个常量
and that times the derivative of the sigmoid function with respect to h1.
然后乘以 h1 对应的 sigmoid 函数的导数
This is something that we calculated below in the instructor comments,
这是我们在讲师注释下面的内容
which is that the sigmoid function has a beautiful derivative,
其中 sigmoid 函数具有很漂亮的导数
namely the derivative of sigmoid of h is
也就是说 σ h 的导数
precisely sigmoid of h times 1 minus sigmoid of h. Again,
是 σ h 乘以 1 - σ h
you can see this development underneath in the instructor comments.
你可以在讲师注释下面看到这个过程
You also have the chance to code this in the quiz because at the end of the day,
你也有机会在练习中编写代码 因为最后
we just code these formulas and then use them forever, and that is it.
我们会编码这些公式 然后长期使用 就是这样
That is how you train a neural network.
这就是你训练神经网络的方法